Our hope in designing this program was to create something that
我们设计这个纳米学位项目的目的
combined the very best materials on offer.
是把所有最好的材料组合在一起提供给大家
We wanted to deliver a class that was better than anything any one person or
我们想要提供一门课程 而且做得比任何事、任何人
organization could do.
或任何机构做的都要好
So we've combined the very best foundational information with exclusive
所以我们将最好的基础知识和独家制作的
new material.
新学习资料相结合
We've also put together a team of the best AI brains on the planet to act as
我们也组建了由这个星球上最强 AI 大脑组成的团队
your guides.
他们会是你的向导
We are delighted, this program features my friend Peter Norvig,
我们很荣幸请到了我的朋友 Peter Norvig
director of research at Google,
Google 的研究主管
who quite literally wrote the leading textbook on artificial intelligence.
他写了人工智能领域最好的教科书
We also meet my friend Thad Starner, who's founder and director
也来见见我的朋友 Thad Starner 他是佐治亚理工学院
of the Contextual Computing Group at Georgia Tech's College of Computing and
计算机系的 Contextual Computing Group 的创始人和主管
a researcher at my very own Google X.
同时也是我自己的 Google X 的研究员
In fact, much of the material in this program is taught to computer science
事实上 这门课中的很多材料 都是世界各地大学用来教
master students around the world including Stanford and Georgia Tech.
计算机研究生的 包括斯坦福和佐治亚理工
I hope that gives you a sense of the quality of the teaching here.
我希望这能让你对我们的教学质量有一个大致的观感
Arpan Chakraborty and David Joyner, will act as further guides on your journey.
Arpan Chakraborty 和 David Joyner 会给你学习旅途提供进一步指导
Arpan has a PhD in computer vision,
Arpan 拥有计算机视觉领域的博士学位
while David won Georgia Tech's Lockheed Excellence Teaching Award and
David 赢得了佐治亚理工的 Lockheed 卓越教学奖
has been lecturing in AI for more than three years.
他 AI 方面拥有超过三年的教学经验
And in the next few videos, Dhruv Parthasarathy who focused on AI for
在接下来的视频中 Dhruv Parthasarathy
both his undergrad and masters degree at MIT.
他在 MIT 的本科和硕士阶段都专注于 AI
And who is the director of the AI Program here at Udacity,
同时也是优达学城的 AI 项目主管
will give you a bird's eye view of this new nanodegree.
将会带你大致了解这个新的纳米学位
You'll even see more of me again.
你也将会多次见到我
So now, over to Dhruv who'll show you what you built during this course.
所以现在 接下来 Dhruv 会展示你将会在这门课中创建什么